

## CONTACT



266 Jones Avenue
Toronto, ON M4M 3A6



e\_howell@live.com 416-670-4846



rixtrixx.com







### **MY STORY**

After over 10 years in customer service, I found myself lacking any challene or motivation in my life. Fast-forward to my coding-life now, and I couldn't have found a more perfect fit!

My transition into web development and coding has been a great journey and learning experience. I have found myself lost spending 8-10 hours at a time working on my projects, and yet I still look forward to the next day.

It has become the first time in my life that I can showcase my artistic side that I could never do before with my clumsy hands. But now with the keyboard I can! Working with JS, React, and CSS, I am constantly challenged that creates a fire within me that leaves me never wanting for motivation. A journey that I hope to continue forever.

# **EDUCATION**

#### Juno College, Toronto ON | 2021

Immersive Web Development Bootcamp: Certificate

Accelerated JavaScript Course
Con-Ed Web Development Course

### York Univeristy, North York ON | 2014

Bachelor of Arts: Specialized Honours in History

### RELEVANT SKILLS

- HTML5, CSS3, SCSS
- JavaScript fundamentals, ¡Query, React
- Working with RESTful APIs, and Firebase
- Responsive design
- Website accessibility requirements

- Version control & collaboration using Git
- Paired programming & team-based development
- Project scope management and time management
- Best practices for modern web development

### **PROJECTS**

-One Piece Coo Delivery Chaptor Selector-

Search specific chapters/arcs in the One Piece series and be given an accurate summarization of each chapter throughout the 1000 chapter saga.

Paired | JS | HTML | | SCSS | API

-What's HOT?-

Check on what is trending across social media. The site updates daily thanks to the TMDB API, so it will always stay up to date!

Solo | React | JSX |
API

### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **SALES ASSOCIATE: EATALY 2019-2020**

- Worked alongside front office representatives to boost sales, specifically in detailing item positioning, location, and aesthetic.
- Was responsible for maintaining an accuracy of sales records, returns and inventory availability

### SERVER/BOX OFFICE: MEDIEVAL TIMES 2016-2019

- Organized seating arrangements for over 1000 people at show, in a timely, orderly, and efficient manner. Guiding team members in the arena, and handling seating issues, and specific dietary restrictions
- Resolved conflicts and negotiated mutually beneficial agreements between parties

### **SALES ASSOCIATE: FRESHII 2014-2015**

- Took lead on a new company venture, where Freshii was
  planning on broadening into delivery. I was their go-to for
  feedback on the programs longevity and its implementation.
  Discussed its benefits to Trade partners alongside with the CEO
  of Freshii All of which led to me to win the first ever Freshii
  Global Ambassador Award
- Trained and developed new staff in delivery procedure